Batuhan Karaduman

Senior Software Engineer

Contact

Address

Istanbul, Istanbul, 34110

Phone

+905319546641

E-mail

batuhankaraduman@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/batuhan-karaduman-ab37

Skills

.Net Core Excellent Asp.Net Excellent SQL Very Good Cloud Computing Good **HTML** Excellent **CSS** Very Good **Javascript** Very Good **Vue.JS** Very Good

Skilled Senior Software engineer with +9 years of experience in a broad range of industries, including banking, corporate website and mobile applications. My main interest is Backend Development with .Net Core and .Net Framework. In Addition, C#, React Native, Vue and a little Cloud Systems. Very communicative person and always interest in learning new things.

Work History

2017-09 - Senior Backend Developer

Current Azerion, Istanbul

I am working as a software developer at Headerlift project. Headerlift is a project that complete monetization platform that maximizes revenue for publishers.

Our architecture had some linux service to calculate the revenue for every partner, Reporting Web UI (written in vue.js), Management UI for intranet and Ad Client application written in .net core which provide ad for website slots.

I worked in all parts of Headerlift system.

Technologies Used: C#, .Net Core, MVC, Web Api, OOP, Cloud Build, Gitlab, HTML, Javascript, Vue.JS, Docker, PostgreSQL, Google Cloud.

2020-08 - **Software Consultant**

Current HEEVI, Istanbul

Heevi is a new startup and mobile marketplace platform of Equipment Rentals. I am working as a Backend (API) developer and learning advanced project management skills. I provide software consultancy.

Heevi is on Android, iOS and Web Platform. I worked in both Web & Backend Part.

Find needed equipments on map, call the owner and DEAL! It is a super app for construction sector.

Technologies Used: C#, .Net Core, Github, .Net Core MVC, Firebase, MySQL for Database & Google Cloud for Hosting.

2019-07 - **Software Consultant**

2021-01

Analizoom, Istanbul

Analizoom, is an online trading & social media platform which you can share your analysis and follow the best analyst to earn money from your crypto investment.

System is integrated with Binance for crypto charts and latest values for every coins. You can trade easily from our portal.

TECHNOLOGIES USED: .Net Core, MySql, AWS for Cloud system, Jetbrains and Docker for continuous integration.

Design Patterns, Object Oriented
Programming

Very Good

Docker, Jenkins, NGINX

Good

React Native

Average

2012-09 -2017-09

Full Stack Developer

Arox, Istanbul

Arox is a software art company. It is a digital agency that has several types of clients in different sectors. I generally developed banking, corporate and mobile application projects.

- VakifEmeklilik is the biggest Private Pension System in Turkey. I worked as a full stack developer in this project.
 We developed intranet application, internet banking (web & mobile applications)
- Beykent University project, it is one of the biggest
 University in Istanbul. We developed website for Beykent.
- Toyota Application, we developed an application for Toyota's industrial workers. It is a tablet application for your car to track maintenance.
- Kido-Fun, is a free kids activities web and mobile portal. I worked in backend - web & APIs side.

TECHNOLOGIES USED: Asp.Net MVC, .Net Framework, MSSQL, C# and Web Technologies.

Education

2008-09 -2013-06

Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering

Istanbul Commerce University - Istanbul

Certifications

2012-06

Bilge Adam Software And Database Expertise

Interests

Docker

Cloud Systems

Data Structures & Algorithms

React Native & Flutter